cebupacificair.com 2014-10-08

# Cebu Pacific Air - Why everyone flies

## Privacy Policy

**CEBU AIR, INC.** (“Cebu Pacific”) takes your privacy seriously. Cebu Pacific is committed to treating t​he personal and corporate information of our users with respect and sensitivity. Our priv​acy commitment is described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is part of our Website Terms of Use.

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers Cebu Pacific's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the Cebu Pacific website – [www.cebupacificair.com](http://www.cebupacificair.com/) (the “Website”), and when you use our products and services. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Cebu Pacific does not own or control, or to people that Cebu Pacific does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collection

Existing immigration, customs, aviation and security laws, rules and regulations of countries where Cebu operates may require collection of personally identifiable information. 

Cebu Pacific collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Cebu Pacific account, when you use certain Cebu Pacific products or services, when you register for Seat Sale Alerts, and when you enter promotions, surveys, contests, competitions or marketing research efforts initiated by Cebu Pacific. 

When you register with Cebu Pacific, you provide us your name, email address, birth date, gender, postcode, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Cebu Pacific will carry out an electronic check to confirm your identity, but may also ask you to provide additional identification, for example if the electronic check is unable to confirm your identity. Cebu Pacific may not be able to provide the products and services to you if do not give Cebu Pacific the above information. Cebu Pacific will not allow any person below eighteen years old to register for a Cebu Pacific account. 

The foregoing notwithstanding, Cebu Pacific has no control over the information you will provide to us and makes no representation as to its accuracy and veracity. We have no means to determine whether or not the information provided to us is complete, accurate, and/or authentic or if you have the legal capacity to transact business with us. If the information is provided about a minor or one who is not legally capable of entering into contractual transactions without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian is responsible for correcting any information given or for informing us that the information should be disregarded or deleted. To the extent permitted by law, Cebu Pacific shall not be liable for any loss, damage or injury whether direct, indirect or consequential, incidental, punitive, exemplary or any other loss, damage or injury arising out of or in connection with the inaccuracies, incompleteness, falsity or errors in the information you provide or by minors or persons who are not legally capable of entering into contractual transactions. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Once you register with Cebu Pacific and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Cebu Pacific also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Cebu Pacific cookie information and the page you requested. 

Cebu Pacific uses "cookies" (small pieces of data Cebu Pacific stores for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make the Website easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and Cebu Pacific. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to the Website. 

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a web site such as www.cebupacificair.com transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the web site can remember who you are. Cookies will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Most browsers have options that allow the visitor to control whether the browser will accept cookies, reject cookies, or notify the visitor each time a cookie is sent. You may elect to reject cookies by adjusting your browser's settings, but doing so will limit the range of features available to the visitor on our site and most other major websites that use cookies. To find out more information about cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Web beacons are used in conjunction with cookies to record the simple actions of the user opening the page that contains the beacon. When a user's browser requests information from a website in this way certain simple information can also be gathered, such as: the IP address of your computer; time the material was viewed; the type of browser that retrieved the image; and the existence of cookies previously set by that server. This is information that is available to any web server you visit. Web beacons do not give any "extra" information away. They are simply a convenient way of gathering the simplest of statistics and managing cookies.” 

### Information Storage

Cebu Pacific holds your information in an electronic file and uses third party information systems providers who may store or have access to your personally identifiable information. Cebu Pacific may also combine previous information you provided us and the personal information that Cebu Pacific may receive about you. 

Cebu Pacific may transfer your personally identifiable information to any of its flight destinations when providing its services to you. Cebu Pacific may also transfer the personally identifiable information between the Philippines, Australia and United Kingdom where its data storage or third party processing facilities are located.

### Information Use

Cebu Pacific may use the information for any legitimate purpose, including but not limited to the following: contacting you in the event of a flight time change or cancellation; credit or other payment card verification/screening; immigration/customs control safety, security, health, administrative; crime prevention/detection; legal purposes, statistical and marketing analysis; systems testing; customer surveys and customer relations communications; to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about special deals and new products.

Cebu Pacific will retain your information for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, or as required by relevant laws.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Cebu Pacific will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Cebu Pacific will only send personally identifiable information about you to third parties when:

  1. We have your consent to share the information;
  2. We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  3. We need to send the information to companies who work on our behalf and to our other contractors;
  4. We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal processes; or
  5. We find that your actions on the Website violate the Website Terms ofUse , or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services

Cebu Pacific reserves its right to disclose your personally identifiable information to our lawyers and legal advisors for establishing, exercising or defending our legal rights. 

Cebu Pacific also reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information in the event of an emergency that threatens the life, health or security of an individual. 

Cebu Pacific may, upon your written request, allow you to access the information that we have stored on you. Further, upon written request and subject to Cebu Pacific’s policy, you may also request correction of your personal information when necessary. You may also contact us at the contact details provided in our website. 

Cebu Pacific reserves the right to charge an administrative fee for providing access. On receipt Cebu Pacific will acknowledge your request and will give you an estimate of when we are able to respond to your request. In certain circumstances, Cebu Pacific reserves the right to deny you access to your personally identifiable information and will provide you with an explanation. 

### Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences

Cebu Pacific gives you the ability to edit your Cebu Pacific Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Cebu Pacific to contact you about specials and new products.

### Information from other websites

Cebu Pacific may institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us. 

Cebu Pacific may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn’t see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as “conversion tracking,” helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. 

Cebu Pacific may receive information about whether or not you’ve seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads. 

### Security

Your Cebu Pacific Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas Cebu Pacific uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. SSL is currently the preferred method to securely transfer credit card and other sensitive data over the Internet. 

In order to improve online experience, Cebu Pacific may track online behavior or click stream data to advance your use of its web pages and track referrals from other websites. Such data will not be stored to your customer record, and will only be aggregated for statistical analysis. 

Cebu Pacific cannot distinguish the age of persons who access and use its websites. If a minor (according to applicable laws) has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the relevant customer information and unsubscribe them. 

### Complaints regarding privacy

Should you have a concern about your privacy or you have any query on your personally identifiable information please write to us or contact us using our contact details as provided in the website. Cebu Pacific will respond to your query or complaint within a reasonable time. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Cebu Pacific may amend this policy from time to time. If Cebu Pacific makes any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the Website. 

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions please contact us here. ​​
